The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal
Subtitles by Bonobosubs
https://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
Mei Ji
Third Ancestor of the Forsaken Immortal Clan
9-Leaf Shaman
I didn't expect
that you would have
a strand of my domain.
Domain ?
Brother...
That soul fragment I got from the Giant Demon Clan Ancestor
was actually hers.
Who are you ?
The cultivators back then
called me Mei Ji.
Note: "Mei Ji" means "Enchantress"
But in the Forsaken Immortal Clan,
I am the Third Ancestor.
So you're the Third Ancestor.
Junior trespassed here by mistake.
I won’t hang around.
Farewell.
Senior, what do you mean by this ?
Compared to "Third Ancestor"
I’d much prefer you call me Mei Ji.
Since you’ve come here today...
I'll let you leave
if you do as I say.
Third Ancestor,
do you know what this is ?
The Billion-Soul Flag !
Since you're hiding here,
it means you must be injured.
Senior, don’t force my hand.
I will now take my leave
and Senior will continue to recover.
What a cautious little cultivator.
The more I look at you, the more I like you.
No one that I fancy
can get away.
Go,
capture him and bring him back here.
Tattoo Beast Atlas
This scroll feels familiar...
This scroll...
why is it similar to our holy treasure ?
The holy treasure of the Forsaken Immortal Clan...
How can he also have a Tattoo Beast Atlas !?
This is bad !
Dragon, tiger, retreat !
Which Ancestor is she ?
She willingly sealed herself inside the Tattoo Beast Atlas...
Who the hell is
this little cultivator ?
After tens of thousands of years...
This old man has finally returned !
Situ Nan
Early stage Ascendant
Senior Situ,
congratulations.
Although I haven’t fully recovered my cultivation,
it’s more than enough for this tiny planet Suzaku.
Now, let’s extract your soul strand from the Cultivation Planet Crystal.
Ancestral Spirit
Forsaken Immortal Clan
Greetings, Ancestral Spirit.
South of the
Suzaku Continent
Greetings, Ancestral Spirit.
Clan members, heed my order.
Begin the chant !
The current forces of Suzaku
are powerless against the Forsaken Immortal Clan.
The two of you will face a life or death trial today.
Whether you can survive it
will depend on your fate.
The Fifth Ancestor of the Forsaken Immortal Clan
pays respects to Zhuque Zi.
Sha Zi
Young Patriarch of the
Forsaken Immortal Clan
The Young Patriarch of the Forsaken Immortal Clan
pays respect to Zhuque Zi.
This humble woman
also pays respects to Zhuque Zi.
Senior Brother,
it has been 3 months.
Have you made your decision ?
You also must have
an 11-Leaf Shaman.
Let me see him.
You promised to split planet Suzaku in two
because you fear the Cultivation Planet Heart in my hands.
If not for it, you would've attacked me long ago.
Why do you bother with all this nonsense ?
However...
if I give you the Cultivation Planet Heart,
wouldn’t that make me some meat on your cutting board !?
I would be at your mercy !
Senior Brother,
I understand your concerns.
This is a Soul-Binding spell.
It will bind your life to the Cultivation Planet Heart.
If my clan betrays you and kills you,
the Cultivation Planet Heart will shatter as well.
My clan
would perish with you.
With this spell,
you can live out your natural lifespan.
Senior Brother,
we don’t want to destroy planet Suzaku.
We just want a way to coexist.
Now give me the Cultivation Planet Heart
and this war can be avoided.
Planet Suzaku will be split in two
and both sides won't interfere with each other.
As expected of my dear Junior Brother,
you’ve calculated everything.
Since you know me so well,
what choice do you think I’ll make now ?
Zhuque Zi,
you’re already at a dead end.
Now accept your defeat !
Suzaku Seal...
attack !
What ?!
The Fifth Ancestor
was killed in an instant ?!
We cannot do anything
against Suzaku Seal attacks
fueled by your lifespan.
Senior Brother,
your lifespan will be exhausted
if you unleash one more strike.
War or peace,
I need your answer.
Junior Brother,
do you remember our master,
the previous Suzaku,
Qian Pinghai ?
You really betrayed him well !
Qian Pinghai,
you were wrong back then !
Terribly wrong !
If you still have a soul, take a good look
at the beloved disciple you appointed as the next Suzaku !
You chose
a descendant of the Forsaken Immortal Clan !
Qian Pinghai,
Yunque Zi and I joined the sect together
and our talents were similar.
But you always favored him
while I
was the odd one.
Just as I lost all hope,
you made me forget it
by passing me the Suzaku Formation,
the legacy of the Suzaku.
I gave it my all to learn to use it.
But I realized
that the Suzaku Formation is a double-edged sword !
Each use damages the Origin Soul.
How could you be so cruel !?
You taught me how to be the Suzaku
but never intended to pass the title to me !
You never imagined
I’d steal the Cultivation Planet Heart before your death
and claim the title of Suzaku for myself
even if I wasn't the one you appointed !
Junior didn't even bury your corpse in the Suzaku Tomb,
I sold it to the Corpse Sect !
This was the only way to alleviate my anger !
Qian Pinghai,
the truth is
that I was the most suited to become the Suzaku !
I bear no hatred towards the Forsaken Immortal Clan.
But my hatred towards you and him is limitless !
Junior Brother,
how could I possibly share this planet with you ?
If I can’t be the first Suzaku,
then I will be the last !
I choose neither of your options.
Cultivation Planet Heart
We will play
a little game together.
If you win
then planet Suzaku is yours.
But if you lose,
then everyone on planet Suzaku will die !
What are you doing !?
Break !
The Cultivation Planet Crystal is in the Suzaku Tomb !
All cultivators under Ascendant
may enter the Suzaku Tomb.
You can try to retrieve your soul strands
or try to get the Cultivation Planet Heart.
But know that when I finally crush this thing to dust,
all those who didn't retrieve their soul strand
will die alongside the Cultivation Planet Crystal !
Be careful !
I will give you 3 months.
You're insane ! You're insane !
The Suzaku Tomb is open.
Everyone,
the game has begun !
This damn brat !
He dared to crush the Cultivation Planet Heart,
he's courting death !
You need your soul strand
in order to survive.
Those who can’t reach the Suzaku Tomb
will all die !
Hurry !
What should we do ?
You're asking now !?
If we had not started this war,
we wouldn't be in such a mess !
Now the lives of our clan are in his hands !
We must play by his rules.
Send all members below 9-Leaf to the Suzaku Tomb.
Proceed with caution.
The rest of us
will look for a solution.
Understood.
This old madman
doesn't want to die alone
so he's trying to drag us all down with him !
Life and death are up to fate.
We must now go out separate ways.
Qian Feng,
remember to use the Suzaku Formation.
And also...
This doll is made from celestial iron.
When you're in danger,
activate its mechanism
and it will save your life.
Understood.
Master.
Qian Pinghai...
I found your descendant,
he has the same Spirit Root you had.
And I treat him just as you once treated me back then.
Our plan is in shambles,
I can no longer enter the Suzaku Tomb now...
You'll have to rely on yourself
to retrieve your soul strand.
The Suzaku Tomb isn’t large,
it's divided into the inner and outer tomb.
You'll first enter the outer tomb.
A single sweep of Divine Sense should help you find an altar.
Pass through it to enter the inner tomb.
There is a mountain at the center,
that is Ye Wuyou’s tomb.
Find the crystal
and retrieve your soul strand.
If you encounter danger and need to leave,
this is the method to break my restrictions.
It should get you out safely.
Understood.
Thank you, Senior.
Entrance of the
Suzaku Tomb
The Suzaku Tomb is opening too slowly...
How can it already be full ?
Since higher cultivation realms entered first
this delays everyone else for no reason !
How is this any different from waiting for death ?
I can’t see through him...
This person isn’t to be trifled with.
How much longer must we wait ?
Stop !
Fellow cultivator,
follow the rules.
The Soul Transformation seniors already entered.
Since we arrived here first,
it will be our turn next.
Since you were late,
you need to wait in the queue.
Don't be rude !
I am Brutal Nan Ming,
my disciple is ignorant.
Please forgive us, Senior.
Master,
what's his cultivation level ?
Why can’t I sense
any spiritual energy from him ?
Of course you can't.
He has shed his mortal roots and must be Late stage Soul Transformation.
Only celestial spiritual energy flows through his meridians.
Ordinary cultivators can't see through him.
It’s open !
It’s open,
go !
Quick !
Hurry inside !
Move !
That gaze…
It feels familiar...
Wang Lin...
You don’t recognize me now,
but I didn't forget about you.
We...
haven’t met each other in a long time.
To let go of the consequences of my actions
is to ignore the law of cause and effect
like scattered ink.
As destiny falls
in exchange for this moment of tainted dreams.
It makes the mountains lose their colors,
wither and melt into rivers.
Who can deceive
the law of the heavens ?
Countless generations
have tried before me.
But how could I not catch my dreams
within my warm fingers ?
You're at my side when I'm alone
giving me the strength to fight the will of the heavens.
Fortunately, my mind was open and honest.
I'm sorry we never got to see the fireworks
in the streets.
Can I break the vortex of our destiny ?
Can I break the rules ?
To run towards you !
I will fight the law of the heavens and the law of cause and effect
to cut down this tribulation with my own hands
and break through the reincarnation cycle.
All of that for the stars in your eyes.
I wish to bend this dream for the fire in my heart.
If your soul is willing to wander,
can I still take your hands
and hold them tight ?
I will defy the heavens and prevent the stars from falling.
I will overthrow the Immortals and the Demons in my heart.
I dream of destroying
the shackles of our fate.
You're the only one that can ignore the law of cause and effect.
You're the hardest to let go of.
I want to be with you again
so I can look in your eyes.
Even for a moment, it's worth it.